I don't call it over the records given to me by the City Council Tuesday, November 18th, 2025.
Number two, public input, that's given to the personal graces.
We have none.
Three A, claims list.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Socle.
Hi.
Jones.
Farther.
Hi.
3B.
The budget amendment 26 that's your run.
I think it's kept reencumbered by a fiscal year, 2425 expenditures for various city-managed funds.
Is that the same one we went over?
No, this is for all the funds that count on this over.
The last one was pretty much it.
Lots of different funds.
General funds, street and alley funds, street and stadium funds.
We'll include your report which will be given to you in a lot of capital funds.
I'll make Washington for this.
This panel is for a lot better than the last one.
Jones.
Hi.
Moons.
Dokel.
Hi.
Easter.
I'm Harper.
Hi.
Three C, two minutes from the November 4th, 2025 record meeting.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Easter.
Hi.
Barn.
Jones.
Hi.
Harper.
Ans, dances and music in the alley.
What has been done with Ottawa County?
We have the county's in civil assembly demolition of the tiger structures?
This is an agreement that Travis and Mike Ferness work out where we will provide limited
will provide limited assistance in demolition of some of the dilapidating houses and structures
that we have in the town and so it's just an agreement that says that they will help us
as funds are available within the city and it was made clear to us in negotiating the agreement
that it would probably be minimal help but we figured that any help was better than that.
They talked about NIMO 2 or 3 at a time and then go to something else and they're coming
back and doing 2 or 3 more so.
But that saves us several thousand dollars every time they do quite any of them, right?
Do we get to pick which ones?
I don't know.
We could.
But take the worst ones.
Yeah.
That's my point.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Double.
Hi.
Barnes.
Three E resolution CC 2025-14.
Sorry.
Bridge.
Inspection.
Second.
Double.
Hi.
Barnes.
Jones.
Hi.
Easton.
Parker.
Hi.
Three E resolution CC 2025-14.
Sorry.
Bridge.
Inspection.
Responsibility by local government for compliance with the National Bridge Inspection Standard
and Robert.
And there.
I'll just turn to Esther.
Esther.
The initiative to continue the guy you're hearing from.
We've been using is in the passenger, my, my, my, my senior.
This is my annual.
Person's testing is also available on the.
So.
And.
I called us.
I make motion to.
So again.
Jones.
First.
High.
Hi.
Thank you three F ordinance 2025 that's 13 providing for real a repeal of section 14 past 25
of chapter 14 of the ordinance regarding jury
qualifications for body separately and establishing effective date
And mayor if you will allow me I can talk about all of these at one time and say the council some time. Okay, so you're going to talk about
3 F 3G 3H which is ordinances 2025 that's 13 2025 that's 14 and 2025 that's 50. Yes, these are
We discussed previously that these are
They really don't apply to us because we don't have jury trials. Therefore, we don't need these in our ordinances
Um, and they affect the feet ordinance so
We discussed our recommended repeal of that because we're never going to have a jury trial in the city of Miami
Um, it's cost prohibitive if nothing else and just so everyone knows we'll be seeing a
Several of these sorts of lists where we're repealing antiquated outdated ordinances to get
Matters in order so that we can put the feet ordinance in
Practice hopefully early
How to make motion to approve and ordinance 2025 that's 13 2025 that's 14 and 2025 that's 15
Second
I'll make motion to approve
Make motion to approve 2025-14 second
All right
Okay, for a nomination to reappoint
Kevin Duffel to the Miami Industrial Public Facilities Authority turn to expire 11, 7, 29
Make motion to approve second
Jones I
Before being a nomination to appoint Scott
To the Miami Public Library Board replacing Christina Ulri kind of expire 11, 21, 26 and just for the board's record this is my father-in-law
so
Just not everybody to be aware and color didn't make me aware of that
before I made my nomination
He's very well qualified. That's very good
background and
Give me a good
I make a motion to approve
All right
You can make a motion
I
For C nomination to appoint Amber Ackinson to the model Public Library Board turn to expire 11, 18, 28
She's somebody's sister
Small-town stuff
Stay
No, sir
Six staff reports
I think the the month of was October really here to see nowhere down 11 percent which I
It's interesting why
Market was amazing great job was I got to see Santa Drowman in by the cops
Yeah, yeah chief come around the corner with this sirens
He did he did he jumped out and was
Getting everybody into the Christmas spirit. So that was awesome. It was a good time
I appreciate it. I hope it grows every year and just continues to be a
Teaping for our holiday shopping kickoff and then also
Leadership Miami this week. So this is my first time ever doing that surprisingly
We got to spend some time in the city doing some various things and we went out to the wastewater treatment plant
and taught Murphy was super
Like I mean obviously knows he's doing these do it for 37 years
But he was very passionate about what he does and and was very well spoken
I mean he did a great job presenting and showing us the various aspects of
Made it interesting, right? I mean, it's it's not really that
It's kind of the you know, it's a dirty part of our process
It's necessary and he went above and beyond to explain how he did it
He even showed us some improvements that they did to reduce their sludge
trips and that's pretty good. So he did a good job. I appreciate it
He he showed well for the city
So after the part when he went and grabbed a handful of the sludge and was showing it to us
That was funny some of the girls were like
Yeah
I want to hop on to what he said about the holiday market
Guys we made that outstand or Tyler ran out standing higher when he higher trended
The trend has done a great job
Everything that we've had downtown is one great
So Kudos to training her team
And I think the things are growing down there and I appreciate all of her efforts
I know sometimes she feels a bit overwhelmed but she's
always makes it go off and
Everybody enjoys it. It's great to see the families downtown smiling all the kids
But junior team doing great. So keep up the great work
Hey city manager community. No sir